hsmglobal.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy | WOBI : World of Business Ideas

WOBI Privacy Policy

HSM Americas Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates ("HSM", "us", "we") are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its products and services, and other users of its site. Your privacy on the Internet is of importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about consumers and users of our site and services, we want to inform you about our privacy policy. Please note that this policy applies only to WOBI, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we may link.

Information About WOBI's Consumers and Users

We will ask you for your personal information when you register at our site; registering with us on our site is optional; however, if you choose not to register, you can still use the web site, but you will not be able to purchase products and services on line. We do not collect any personal information regarding your use of the site, when you are just browsing it. We need certain information about you in order to provide you with the product or service requested by you (i.e. name, billing address, credit card number, phone number). We also collect information for market research purposes to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which of services are of most interest to them. When registering, you are authorizing us to also use this information to let you know about new products or services that may be of your interest. (Please see Disclosure below).

When registering, our site sets a cookie that will allow us to provide you with a more customized experience on our site; thus, enabling you to manage your subscriptions and online profile, remembering you the next time you visit, helping you find information more easily, and confirming your purchases and registrations on our site. Also, our site registers your IP address, and other information regarding your operating system and browser. This information is never connected with the personal information you supply to us if you register on our website.

Disclosure

WOBI takes your privacy very seriously. The information submitted by you to us, will be used for registration and administrative purposes. When registering with us at our site, you expressly agree and authorize us to use your information (name, address, email address or telephone number) to help us provide the products and services you have requested, and keep you informed of offers that may be of your interest. Additionally, you expressly agree that we may share your information both (i) with other HSM Group companies and (ii) with our business partners. You hereby further accept and authorize us to share your information with other reputable companies outside of the HSM Group both within and outside the USA to keep you informed of offers that may be of interest to you. They may wish to contact you either in writing, by mail, by fax or by e-mail.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, physical threat, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, in which disclosure is necessary.

Security

We employ a range of technologies to protect your information in our systems from misuse, destruction, loss, and unauthorized disclosure. However effective our measures are, we cannot guarantee the security of the database.

Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to change these Terms. If we change these terms, those changes will be posted here for your information. We further reserve the discretionary right to modify any features of this site or services provided there in at any time.

Applicable law and jurisdiction

This Agreement will be interpreted by the laws of the State of New York with regards to contracts executed and fully performed therein. You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising out of or relating to these Terms or your use of this site shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in the State of New York .

General Provisions

This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and HSM, superseding any prior or contemporaneous, either oral or written communications.

Termination

We reserve the discretionary right to terminate your access to all or part of this site, with or without notice.

How to Contact Us: If you have any questions or concerns about the HSM Privacy Policy, please contact us at
